[
    {
        "question": "Domain Name",
        "answer": "Your first step towards digitalisation. Book and secure your unique, easy-to-remember domain name with Edneed, before anybody else does."
    },
    {
        "question": "Subdomain",
        "answer": "Get a FREE Edneed subdomain with a domain. It will act like a mirror image of your website, if your domain is down for due to any technical reason."
    },
    {
        "question": "Secure Website Hosting",
        "answer": "Your website will be securely hosted with Edneed's server."
    },
    {
        "question": "Guard it with SSL",
        "answer": "SSL stands for Secured Sockets Layer. SSL certification helps your websites to keep their data secure, prevents them from attack and conveys a trust factor to the end users."
    },
    {
        "question": "Website Builder",
        "answer": "A one-stop solution website builder with a live editor to create a phenomenal digital presence for your institute. No coding or developers needed."
    },
    {
        "question": "Admission ",
        "answer": "Tell your website visitors when admissions are open and accept applications through your website itself."
    },
    {
        "question": "Vacancy",
        "answer": "Looking for teachers? Recruit via your website. Make positions open and accept applications."
    },
    {
        "question": "Services",
        "answer": "Attract visitors by mentioning special services offered by our institute."
    },
    {
        "question": "Announcements",
        "answer": "Keep the communication clear. Display notifications on your website easily."
    },
    {
        "question": "Fee Structure",
        "answer": "Upload fee structure of special courses, trips or classes. Add payment methods."
    },
    {
        "question": "Payment Method",
        "answer": "Add multiple payment method details such as; Cheque, UPI, PayPal and Bank Account."
    },
    {
        "question": "Gallery",
        "answer": "Upload beautiful videos and pictures to your website. Create multiple albums to attract visitors."
    },
    {
        "question": "Testimonial",
        "answer": "Put up positive experiences of your stakeholders on your website. It builds credibility in front of visitors."
    },
    {
        "question": "WhatsApp Support Centre",
        "answer": "Always be available to answer customer queries with WhatsApp Support Centre."
    }
    
]